

□+1 (734) 496-1803 | ■jwnchung@umich.edu | ★ jaewonchung.me | □ jaywonchung

Summary .

I am a second year PhD student in CSE at the University of Michigan, advised by Professor Mosharaf Chowdhury. My research interest is in the intersection of software systems and deep learning, with a recent focus in energy consumption. I lead the ML Energy initiative (https://ml.energy).

Education

University of Michigan

Ann Arbor, MI, USA

Ph.D. STUDENT IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Sep 2021 - present

Seoul National University

B.S. IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Seoul, South Korea Mar 2015 - Aug 2021

- GPA: 4.04/4.3 (overall) 4.15/4.3 (major)
- Summa Cum Laude
- · Period includes two years of military service, required to all Korean men.

Publications

- Zeus: Understanding and Optimizing GPU Energy Consumption of DNN Training, Jie You*, Jae-Won Chung*, Mosharaf Chowdhury, 20th USENIX Symposium on Networked Systems Design and Implementation (NSDI), 2023 (Acceptance rate = 18.38%)
- ShadowTutor: Distributed Partial Distillation for Mobile Video DNN Inference, Jae-Won Chung, Jae-Yun Kim, Soo-Mook Moon, 49th International Conference on Parallel Processing (ICPP), 2020 (Acceptance rate = 28.99%)

Experience _____

SymbioticLab UMich, United States

GRADUATE STUDENT RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Sep 2022 - Present

- Advised by Professor Mosharaf Chowdhury.
- · Zeus: Understanding and optimizing GPU energy consumption of DNN training

Software Platform Lab SNU, South Korea

RESEARCH INTERN

Apr 2020 - Jun 2022

- Advised by Professor Byung-Gon Chun.
- Crane: A GPU cluster manager for AutoML workloads. Extensive systems programming and research on cluster scheduling policies.

Virtual Machine and Optimization Lab

SNU, South Korea

• Advised by Professor Soo-Mook Moon.

Dec 2019 - Jun 2020

• ShadowTutor: Server-client collaborative video DNN inference. Use of knowledge distillation reduced network data transfer by 95%.

Computer Vision Lab SNU, South Korea

Undergraduate Intern

SENIOR PROJECT

Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

Advised by Professor Kyoung Mu Lee.

• Better meta-initialization methods for Model-Agnostic Meta-Learning (MAML) with neural memory modules and convex programs.

Lab of Imaging Science and Technology

SNU, South Korea

Undergraduate Intern

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Advised by Professor Jongho Lee.
- · Designed and implemented a full deep learning pipeline for Quantitative Susceptibility Mapping. Accumulated experience on 3D MRI field data.

August 29, 2022 Jae-Won Chung · Résumé

^{*} equal contribution

Honors & Awards

Jul 2021 **Kwanjeong Overseas Scholarship,** Kwanjeong Educational Foundation, \$100,000 over four years
Mar 2019 **Kwanjeong Undergraduate Scholarship,** Kwanjeong Educational Foundation, \$20,000 over two years

Seoul, South Korea Seoul, South Korea

Teaching

- Spring 2021 Operating Systems, Main TA, Managed course projects and led group design reviews.
- Fall 2020 Computer Organization (Undergraduate architecture), Peer tutor, Provided 30 hours of online lecture, Best Tutor Award!

Skills

Language Python, Rust, CUDA, C++, Verilog, C, Bash

Framework PyTorch, Pandas, Matplotlib

Methodology Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Multi-Armed Bandit

Tool Docker, Kubernetes, LaTeX

English TOEFL 120 (Perfect score, Feb 2020), GRE 167/170/4.5 (Mar 2018), TOEIC 990 (Perfect score, Oct 2018)